<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-03-13T14:24:17+05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My Jekyll Website</title><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/03/11/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2021-03-11T02:31:32+05:00</published><updated>2021-03-11T02:31:32+05:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/03/11/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/03/11/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll requires blog post files to be named according to the following format:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR-MONTH-DAY-title.MARKUP&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR&lt;/code&gt; is a four-digit number, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MONTH&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;DAY&lt;/code&gt; are both two-digit numbers, and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MARKUP&lt;/code&gt; is the file extension representing the format used in the file. After that, include the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Curiefense GA (1.3.0) Released</title><link href="/2021/03/02/curiefense-ga-1-3-0-released-project-joins-cncf-sandbox-launches-new-learning-platform-and-more.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Curiefense GA (1.3.0) Released" /><published>2021-03-02T00:00:00+05:00</published><updated>2021-03-02T00:00:00+05:00</updated><id>/2021/03/02/curiefense-ga-1-3-0-released-project-joins-cncf-sandbox-launches-new-learning-platform-and-more</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/03/02/curiefense-ga-1-3-0-released-project-joins-cncf-sandbox-launches-new-learning-platform-and-more.html">&lt;p&gt;
    Curiefense is now in GA! 🎉 The &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.curiefense.io/v/1.3.0/installation/getting-started-with-curiefense&quot;&gt;latest version&lt;/a&gt; (1.3.0) is now available for deployment. A lot has happened since the initial release of v1.0
    in November, and not just in &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.curiefense.io/v/1.3.0/reference/release-notes&quot;&gt;our changelog&lt;/a&gt;. Here are some of the highlights.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Joining the Open Source and Cloud Native Communities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Curiefense is now a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.curiefense.io/post/now-a-cncf-sandbox-project&quot;&gt;CNCF Sandbox Project&lt;/a&gt;, and we’re already making substantial progress in conforming the project to CNCF standards.&amp;nbsp;
    &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The project has &lt;a href=&quot;https://bestpractices.coreinfrastructure.org/en/projects/4576&quot;&gt;earned the CII Best Practices Badge&lt;/a&gt; from the Linux Foundation.
    &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    We have launched a podcast: “ &lt;a href=&quot;https://ctcn.fireside.fm/1&quot;&gt;Committing to Cloud Native&lt;/a&gt;.” Along with discussing news and current events in the community, we’ll be documenting our journey as we integrate Curiefense into the
    cloud native ecosystem. Hopefully, the lessons we learn along the way can be useful to others who travel this path later.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;New Interactive Learning Platform&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Now you can try Curiefense without having to install anything. Our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.katacoda.com/curiefense/scenarios/getting-started&quot;&gt;first scenario on Katacoda&lt;/a&gt; provides you with a live, remotely-accessible environment, and
    walks you through Curiefense’s initial deployment, management UI, and dashboards. More scenarios are on the way. Be sure to check out our short &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HkoDPW46a8I&quot;&gt;explainer video&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Project Transparency and Community Participation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Curiefense has been an “open book” project from day one, and we’re continuing to make data even easier to access. Recently we have:
    &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        Created a
        &lt;a href=&quot;https://app.databox.com/datawall/3ddf913b2db3bb4f53586ec27aaee63106008ba72&quot;&gt;GitHub Dashboard by Databox&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        Added
        &lt;a href=&quot;https://curiefense.devstats.cncf.io/d/8/dashboards?orgId=1&amp;amp;from=now-7d&amp;amp;to=now-1h&amp;amp;refresh=15m&quot;&gt;activity reporting via CNCF DevStats&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        Created multiple granular channels in the Curiefense Slack workspace, making it easier to follow and participate in specific parts in the project. Slack members can interact with project maintainers, and can also subscribe to our
        realtime GitHub repository feed.
    &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;w-richtext-figure-type-image w-richtext-align-center&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/5fa1500e10bda4bfdcb1b209/603d1f417e492c8d476094cf_8TxW2CC76Y5PPK724sbfuKUYj45-nKtkomQVjv0NG2n38a6ajhYrzbA_FNlDX5ud8BkafIweJ7uor_WF-dvSTDsDmmyWK3lXOK180j2rFOT3XaHK3MClYjtVrAARmPVMBMFrFt27.png&quot; width=&quot;auto&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; loading=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    To join the Curiefense workspace on Slack, just email &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:community@curiefense.io&quot;&gt;community@curiefense.io&lt;/a&gt; for an invite.
    &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    To follow us elsewhere, Twitter ( &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/curiefense&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/curiefense&lt;/a&gt;) is our most-used social media channel. If you prefer email, we also have a
    &lt;a href=&quot;http://eepurl.com/hnnmpj&quot;&gt;newsletter&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Fun Stuff&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    To celebrate our launch, we now have &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/curiefense/media/blob/main/README.md#-wallpaper&quot;&gt;Curiefense wallpaper&lt;/a&gt; available for your
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/curiefense/media/blob/main/README.md#-wallpaper&quot;&gt;desktop&lt;/a&gt; and/or &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/curiefense/media/blob/main/README.md#-zoom-virtual-backgrounds&quot;&gt;Zoom&lt;/a&gt;. Stay tuned for shirts and stickers,
    coming soon!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;All Are Welcome!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    Curiefense is maintained by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reblaze.com/&quot;&gt;Reblaze&lt;/a&gt;, which is making significant investments into its development. That being said, Curiefense is a CNCF project, and is vendor-neutral.&amp;nbsp;
    &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    We ask anyone who is interested to join us (including competitors). Our goal is to provide the community with a robust cloud native security solution for Envoy Proxy, and all are welcome. The more we work together, the better it will be
    for everyone.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Acknowledgments and Thanks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The Curiefense team would like to thank:&amp;nbsp;
    &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/amye&quot;&gt;Amye Scavarda Perrin&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/cra&quot;&gt;Chris Aniszczyk&lt;/a&gt; at the CNCF with onboarding&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        Our advisors: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mattklein123&quot;&gt;Matt Klein&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ChrisUeland&quot;&gt;Chris Ueland&lt;/a&gt;, Chris Ferreira, James Bynoe, and the rest of
        &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.curiefense.io/about-us&quot;&gt;the team&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/g_uist&quot;&gt;Kerollany “Guist”&lt;/a&gt; for her awesome merch designs&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        Stephen and Emilia at O’Reilly for their help with
        &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.katacoda.com/curiefense&quot;&gt;our Katacoda scenarios&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Curiefense is now in GA! 🎉 The latest version (1.3.0) is now available for deployment. A lot has happened since the initial release of v1.0 in November, and not just in our changelog. Here are some of the highlights. Joining the Open Source and Cloud Native Communities Curiefense is now a CNCF Sandbox Project, and we’re already making substantial progress in conforming the project to CNCF standards.&amp;nbsp; The project has earned the CII Best Practices Badge from the Linux Foundation. We have launched a podcast: “ Committing to Cloud Native.” Along with discussing news and current events in the community, we’ll be documenting our journey as we integrate Curiefense into the cloud native ecosystem. Hopefully, the lessons we learn along the way can be useful to others who travel this path later.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; New Interactive Learning Platform Now you can try Curiefense without having to install anything. Our first scenario on Katacoda provides you with a live, remotely-accessible environment, and walks you through Curiefense’s initial deployment, management UI, and dashboards. More scenarios are on the way. Be sure to check out our short explainer video. Project Transparency and Community Participation Curiefense has been an “open book” project from day one, and we’re continuing to make data even easier to access. Recently we have: Created a GitHub Dashboard by Databox Added activity reporting via CNCF DevStats Created multiple granular channels in the Curiefense Slack workspace, making it easier to follow and participate in specific parts in the project. Slack members can interact with project maintainers, and can also subscribe to our realtime GitHub repository feed. To join the Curiefense workspace on Slack, just email community@curiefense.io for an invite. To follow us elsewhere, Twitter ( https://twitter.com/curiefense) is our most-used social media channel. If you prefer email, we also have a newsletter.&amp;nbsp; Fun Stuff To celebrate our launch, we now have Curiefense wallpaper available for your desktop and/or Zoom. Stay tuned for shirts and stickers, coming soon! All Are Welcome! Curiefense is maintained by Reblaze, which is making significant investments into its development. That being said, Curiefense is a CNCF project, and is vendor-neutral.&amp;nbsp; We ask anyone who is interested to join us (including competitors). Our goal is to provide the community with a robust cloud native security solution for Envoy Proxy, and all are welcome. The more we work together, the better it will be for everyone. Acknowledgments and Thanks The Curiefense team would like to thank:&amp;nbsp; Amye Scavarda Perrin, and Chris Aniszczyk at the CNCF with onboarding Our advisors: Matt Klein, Chris Ueland, Chris Ferreira, James Bynoe, and the rest of the team Kerollany “Guist” for her awesome merch designs Stephen and Emilia at O’Reilly for their help with our Katacoda scenarios</summary></entry></feed>